{"_id":{"$oid":"642564d0330bf91bd3102a4b"},"product_asin":"B08KGVWZCC","QAs":[{"question":"Does it contain pockets?","answer":"Yes, the product has 2 pockets","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-03-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564d1330bf91bd3102a4d"},"product_asin":"B07GRSCBLM","QAs":[{"question":"What's the size like 38 or 40 or 42?","answer":"40","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2020-09-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564d1330bf91bd3102a4f"},"product_asin":"B08FB8JPV2","QAs":[{"question":"Is large same as size 42 ?","answer":"L refers to size 40.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-10-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564d2330bf91bd3102a51"},"product_asin":"B07DW85TC5","QAs":[{"question":"Does this product include both Kurta and Pyjama?","answer":"Yes, it has both kurta and pyjama","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Gupta","date":"2022-10-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the chest size of XXL","answer":"44","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-09-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564d4330bf91bd3102a54"},"product_asin":"B08KGH3QGL","QAs":[{"question":"I'm a faat man, is this regular fit or slim fit?","answer":"This is regular fit Kurta","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the product from the original brand?","answer":"Yes.. directly from the brand Manyavar","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-06-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564d4330bf91bd3102a57"},"product_asin":"B017D4SI3G","QAs":[{"question":"My chest size is 38 which size is perfectly fitting?","answer":"If your chest is 38 then you should go for Medium size or you can also check our size chart.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2020-01-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the fabric blend? Silk ? Cotton ?","answer":"Blend","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2020-03-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need an black Churidar (size - XL) for this kurta, where do i get it?","answer":"I would like to let you know that black churidar has already included with this kurta set. You will get the black churidar by placing an order of XL size.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2020-01-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"In size chart given measurement is of cloth or the person himself","answer":"Cloth","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-11-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"These are regular fit / comfort fit kurtas (not slim fit), right?","answer":"Regular fit","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-09-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest is 30. which size is good for me","answer":"The size 30 is not sold by us currently.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is 39 ..can I go for 36/38","answer":"I think you should go for 38","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2018-12-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"White churidar available?","answer":"Not available with this kurta set","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2018-12-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"46 size available?","answer":"Dear Sir","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2018-10-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"My cheast size is 42,which is perfect for me l or xl???","answer":"L","votes":"0","username":"Jeetendra j.","date":"2018-10-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564d6330bf91bd3102a63"},"product_asin":"B07D5XMJS2","QAs":[{"question":"Is this Green or yellow?","answer":"Yellow","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-01-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"ihad wanted aManyavar yellow kurta churidar set not a green.  is a yellow one available pl","answer":"The product is yellow in color as showing in the picture. You may order this for yellow requirement.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-11-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this Green or yellow?","answer":"Yellow","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-07-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564d7330bf91bd3102a68"},"product_asin":"B01GOE6TAA","QAs":[{"question":"Is this set suitable for sleepwear ?","answer":"Yes Sir...you may use it as sleepwear too other than special occasions","votes":"0","username":"Someshwar Singh Naryal","date":"2022-11-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pyjamas is drawstring?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"what size will be required for 42 inches chest size","answer":"You may go for XL size","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Size is there any replacement policy","answer":"Yes you can return it back to sender if it is unfit to you by putting back it in it's packing without removing tags or spoiling the cloth by going back to amazon app therein finding return/cancellation option or calling customer care, its that simple","votes":"0","username":"Someshwar Singh Naryal","date":"2021-12-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do I check the actual measurements of size 36 and 38","answer":"If body is slim then only 36.","votes":"0","username":"Sanjay Gupta","date":"2021-09-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do these payjamas have pockets ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rohatgi","date":"2021-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"may i wear this on id day","answer":"Excellent","votes":"0","username":"PINAKIN R LEUVA","date":"2021-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Need xl size. When will it be available?","answer":"Very soon when you click on the option given just below where this product is shown","votes":"0","username":"Someshwar Singh Naryal","date":"2021-12-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Returnable or not ??","answer":"Yes it is","votes":"0","username":"Someshwar Singh Naryal","date":"2021-12-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this slim fit or regular fit","answer":"Regular fit","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2020-10-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564d9330bf91bd3102a75"},"product_asin":"B08F8Z5G4R","QAs":[{"question":"Does this have inner lining in it","answer":"Yes it has an inner lining","votes":"0","username":"Shalini Mittal","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether exchange or return is possible?","answer":"Yes exchange was possible","votes":"0","username":"Shalini Mittal","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do it get shrink?","answer":"No. I washed at home","votes":"0","username":"Mousumi","date":"2021-08-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564da330bf91bd3102a7b"},"product_asin":"B08QFD82QJ","QAs":[{"question":"Or color mil sakta hai","answer":"Currently this comes in only this color.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-12-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it come with pyjama?","answer":"The price is inclusive of a lower (churidar)","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-11-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564dc330bf91bd3102a7e"},"product_asin":"B017D4H1NO","QAs":[{"question":"What size fit if shirts size is xxl and waist is 36","answer":"XXL","votes":"0","username":"MUSFIA HUSSAIN","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What size will fit if its M  in Levis?","answer":"38","votes":"0","username":"Managobinda s.","date":"2019-10-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What size will fit if its M  in Levis?","answer":"Size XXI  Fits","votes":"0","username":"Mohammed Fakhruddin","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"my chest size is 38 so whih size i go for it","answer":"38","votes":"0","username":"MUSFIA HUSSAIN","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564dc330bf91bd3102a83"},"product_asin":"B07GS8Y8BD","QAs":[{"question":"Is it fsbric cotton blended","answer":"This is silk blended.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564dd330bf91bd3102a85"},"product_asin":"B07TWFD4YL","QAs":[{"question":"I want this kurta in L size but only small size is available","answer":"https://www.amazon.in/dp/B07TT9YPNK?ref=myi_title_dp","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-09-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"XL size in cm?","answer":"If the chest round measurement is 105cm to 108 cm, you may go for XL size.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which size kurta should one order if his shirt size is 40?","answer":"You may order size L","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the fabric of the kurta?","answer":"This is blended fabric (Mix of Cotton & Silk)","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-10-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564dd330bf91bd3102a8a"},"product_asin":"B07QHJNZCN","QAs":[{"question":"Is it available in size 42?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-04-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564df330bf91bd3102a8d"},"product_asin":"B07FF7QFRM","QAs":[{"question":"Does it consist pant?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Atul","date":"2020-07-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have pockets? If yes, how many?","answer":"Yes, this kurta has 2 pockets","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2020-01-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Send me a size chart","answer":"You can see the size chart on the product detail page.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-05-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e0330bf91bd3102a91"},"product_asin":"B07JKMJMPH","QAs":[{"question":"Is this cotton?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Ashish singh","date":"2021-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What size should be perfect for 5'9 guy","answer":"Large size of this one","votes":"0","username":"Vikram","date":"2021-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Comes with pyjama?","answer":"Yes,","votes":"0","username":"Vikram","date":"2021-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this Kurta have lining??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-05-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e1330bf91bd3102a97"},"product_asin":"B08F8J6KGH","QAs":[{"question":"Does this have inner lining in it","answer":"Yes it has an inner lining","votes":"0","username":"Shalini Mittal","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether exchange or return is possible?","answer":"Yes exchange was possible","votes":"0","username":"Shalini Mittal","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do it get shrink?","answer":"No. I washed at home","votes":"0","username":"Mousumi","date":"2021-08-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e1330bf91bd3102a9b"},"product_asin":"B07TT9YPNK","QAs":[{"question":"I want this kurta in L size but only small size is available","answer":"https://www.amazon.in/dp/B07TT9YPNK?ref=myi_title_dp","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-09-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"XL size in cm?","answer":"If the chest round measurement is 105cm to 108 cm, you may go for XL size.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which size kurta should one order if his shirt size is 40?","answer":"You may order size L","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the fabric of the kurta?","answer":"This is blended fabric (Mix of Cotton & Silk)","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-10-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e2330bf91bd3102aa0"},"product_asin":"B017D4SIMM","QAs":[{"question":"My chest size is 38 which size is perfectly fitting?","answer":"If your chest is 38 then you should go for Medium size or you can also check our size chart.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2020-01-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the fabric blend? Silk ? Cotton ?","answer":"Blend","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2020-03-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need an black Churidar (size - XL) for this kurta, where do i get it?","answer":"I would like to let you know that black churidar has already included with this kurta set. You will get the black churidar by placing an order of XL size.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2020-01-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"In size chart given measurement is of cloth or the person himself","answer":"Cloth","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-11-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"These are regular fit / comfort fit kurtas (not slim fit), right?","answer":"Regular fit","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-09-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest is 30. which size is good for me","answer":"The size 30 is not sold by us currently.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is 39 ..can I go for 36/38","answer":"I think you should go for 38","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2018-12-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"White churidar available?","answer":"Not available with this kurta set","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2018-12-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"46 size available?","answer":"Dear Sir","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2018-10-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"My cheast size is 42,which is perfect for me l or xl???","answer":"L","votes":"0","username":"Jeetendra j.","date":"2018-10-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e4330bf91bd3102aad"},"product_asin":"B071S151G6","QAs":[{"question":"Is it of pure cotton","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Darsh Creations","date":"2020-11-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it of pure cotton?","answer":"Yes. Pure cotton","votes":"0","username":"Banjagere Jayaprakash","date":"2020-11-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the size","answer":"Below are the links to all the sizes38 -https://www.amazon.in/dp/B071VLWT8740 -https://www.amazon.in/dp/B071459MRJ42 -https://www.amazon.in/dp/B071HNP6C444 -https://www.amazon.in/dp/B071S151G6Hope it helps. Thanks, Vastramay familysee less","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2017-12-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e5330bf91bd3102ab3"},"product_asin":"B07CPRWWNZ","QAs":[{"question":"Title mentions black. but details mentions navy blue. is this black or navy blue?","answer":"Navy blue","votes":"0","username":"MMH Beg","date":"2021-10-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Title mentioned black, but pictures show navy blue. ?","answer":"Navy blue","votes":"0","username":"MMH Beg","date":"2021-10-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can wascoat is with dress","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"MMH Beg","date":"2021-10-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e5330bf91bd3102ab7"},"product_asin":"B07S3WXFGY","QAs":[{"question":"I need 42 size. When will it be available?","answer":"Dear Customer,Due to the constant increase in Orders, this size is currently not in stock.We keep on updating our stock everyday.Thanks & Regardssee less","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2020-11-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e5330bf91bd3102ab9"},"product_asin":"B07CQNKC9Q","QAs":[{"question":"Is it of pure cotton..?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-10-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest size is 40 which size suitable for me?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Hariprasad prajapati","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest size is 40 which size suitable for me?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Hariprasad prajapati","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is Large (L) and my paint size is 32 which is fit for me","answer":"Yes ok","votes":"0","username":"Hariprasad prajapati","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is 40. My height is 168 cms which size is suitable for t","answer":"You may go for size 42.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-11-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is 40 and my hight is 5.8 which is fit for me","answer":"Go for 42.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-11-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e6330bf91bd3102ac0"},"product_asin":"B07S4L19V2","QAs":[{"question":"My shirt size 40. Which size fit for me.","answer":"L size will fit.","votes":"0","username":"Dipankar Maurya","date":"2019-10-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is 38 . Which size is fit for me ?","answer":"40","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-08-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 3 piece or only jacket","answer":"3 piece full set.","votes":"0","username":"JBN Creation","date":"2018-11-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e6330bf91bd3102ac4"},"product_asin":"B07NH1H512","QAs":[{"question":"How to know the men size....the mentioned number is for chest or age for men","answer":"Order according to your shirt size","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-12-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to select  size  dad & son","answer":"Your shirt size","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-12-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get my stuff early delivery","answer":"Prime members","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-12-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it puore silk","answer":"how can u expect Pure silk  at such cheap cost","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-10-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this available with modi jacket","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-10-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is chest size for 36 man in your product","answer":"36 only","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-10-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this product returnable?","answer":"I don't know hether is returnable","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-10-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Family dress set father mother and child like king queen and children  photo picture in heart shape","answer":"U don't pic uploading option her","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-10-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get early delivery","answer":"Dear Customer,Greetings of the Day!We would like to inform you that most of our orders are fulfilled by Amazon wherein Amazon looks after the logistics.We would also like to inform you that the material is in stock & can be immediately dispatched.Hence, we would request you to place the order.Happy Shopping!JBN Creations | VASTRAMAYsee less","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2020-08-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Men kurta xl or baby 3 year which size are perfect in above list","answer":"Perfectly fit and nice but the child was a bit older.","votes":"0","username":"DEEPAK KUMAR BACHHAL","date":"2020-07-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e8330bf91bd3102acf"},"product_asin":"B07283VW4V","QAs":[{"question":"Height is 5'5 which size is perfect","answer":"don't buy from amazon","votes":"0","username":"NARESH DEVADI","date":"2020-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"We will get full dress","answer":"Dear Customer,Please click on the below link to buy complete set.https://www.amazon.in/dp/B07D8TWB6F?ref_=dpLinkThankssee less","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2020-10-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"when this item delivered???","answer":"i got defect product from amazon. i did not get replacement also","votes":"0","username":"NARESH DEVADI","date":"2020-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"My hip size is 46 cm will this suite me","answer":"Yeh...","votes":"0","username":"m r moinuddin","date":"2019-08-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"My height is 6 feet.chest is 43 inches (tightly measured)....in kurta pajamas it is difficult to choose correct measurement no. option...kindly phone","answer":"I think XL would be fine for you. But minor alterations are required for body fitting.","votes":"0","username":"Raghavendra K R","date":"2019-07-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest is 36 which one will be best??","answer":"I would suggest you should bu size 38","votes":"0","username":"Harish Khatri","date":"2019-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is measurment for small size?","answer":"No idea, please check on Amazon site.","votes":"0","username":"Harish Khatri","date":"2019-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"I wear a shirt of size 40 regular fit, which size I should go for this product?","answer":"This product is very nice","votes":"0","username":"Hariprasad prajapati","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size l so which size is com3?","answer":"This product fabric is very bad.. don’t purchase this","votes":"0","username":"Ravinder Singh","date":"2019-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest size is 34 and height is 174 cm. which size should i go for","answer":"Bad quality product","votes":"0","username":"Ravinder Singh","date":"2019-05-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e9330bf91bd3102adb"},"product_asin":"B071VLSQJH","QAs":[{"question":"What is the length of the sleeves?","answer":"Depends on the size you will order","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-11-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it really made by silk & cotton ?","answer":"No it's like synthetic little rough","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest size 38 solder 18 to mera size kya hoga","answer":"Xl try karate Tora tight hai sizes","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"If size not fitted then how to return ??","answer":"Prime member","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this man comes free with kurta and pajama ?","answer":"No this men is not original only for a dammy purpose but if you order it they will send you kurta or pajama set of good quality","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is its size","answer":"Xxxl","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pant is elestic or not","answer":"Not elestic","votes":"0","username":"DEEPAK S.","date":"2021-12-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to check pant size","answer":"There is free size pzama , it's narrow and zero size legs","votes":"0","username":"DEEPAK S.","date":"2021-12-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is xl which sixe i want to buy ?","answer":"42 Inc will perfect for you if you are healthy or 40 also came in xl","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please send my order early","answer":"Let amazon customer service know about it","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564e9330bf91bd3102ae6"},"product_asin":"B07D8TRBKG","QAs":[{"question":"my height is 5.3 what size will suit me ? and what is the cloth material ?","answer":"I had bought 40 size , which fits perfect on me .","votes":"0","username":"Raj","date":"2022-11-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"My height is 5.11 and weight is 85 kg plz tell me the correct size dhoti kurta  for for me","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suits for 6 feet?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size  & jeans(trouser size) is xl & 36 respectively, which size will be comfortable to me?","answer":"Hi.... try xxl...it's fit for u","votes":"0","username":"m r moinuddin","date":"2019-08-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"this suits fr a 5.6 height","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Hariprasad prajapati","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564eb330bf91bd3102aed"},"product_asin":"B093DQMP4Z","QAs":[{"question":"What size is this Kurta Pajama?","answer":"This is size 46. (XXXL)","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-11-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564ec330bf91bd3102aef"},"product_asin":"B07XZNC9RQ","QAs":[{"question":"can I get this dress only for my kid?","answer":"Yes you can. Please contact the brand directly. Thanks","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2020-07-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564ec330bf91bd3102af1"},"product_asin":"B07CQMGGHN","QAs":[{"question":"shervani with pant..?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anush paul","date":"2021-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hi can i get the white one in 44 size","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anush paul","date":"2021-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Shoes available","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Anush paul","date":"2021-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Meterial","answer":"not pure cotton..silk type","votes":"0","username":"Nimesh Patel","date":"2021-02-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How return or refund is possible?","answer":"Return in 30 days possible and refund in2hrs","votes":"0","username":"Anush paul","date":"2021-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is dhoti with the servani or not","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for showing interest in our Ensemble.We would like to let you know that this is a Sherwani Set and hence you will get the Kurta as well as the Dhoti.Please place order for \"Vastramay Men's Black Cotton Sherwani Set\" for the complete look.Keep Shopping.VASTRAMAYsee less","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2020-09-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it semi stitched or ready to wear","answer":"It's ready to wear.","votes":"0","username":"Rishabh Awadhiya","date":"2020-08-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it returnable ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rishabh Awadhiya","date":"2020-08-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want only sheerwani with out pyjama","answer":"Seller doesn't sell sherwani separate.","votes":"0","username":"Rishabh Awadhiya","date":"2020-08-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get this white serwani in 42 size","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anush paul","date":"2021-05-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564ef330bf91bd3102b00"},"product_asin":"B07D8VCB1Q","QAs":[{"question":"My hight is 5'3 which size prefer for me","answer":"Go with the 'S' one. Probably u might need to get altering as per ur size on pajamas.","votes":"0","username":"saurav singh","date":"2022-09-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is 40. And i am 6.1inch. tall me  my size","answer":"42","votes":"0","username":"SOURAV SANTRA","date":"2021-10-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"My heights is 5.6 which size is perfect","answer":"43","votes":"0","username":"SOURAV SANTRA","date":"2021-10-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"My height is 5.5 and chest is 36 what size suits me ?","answer":"Yeah","votes":"0","username":"Prasanna ppk","date":"2021-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"my height is 6 ft but I'm skinny, please help me?","answer":"Go for medium size then.","votes":"0","username":"Saish rivanker","date":"2021-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"My height is 6\"4which size is fit 4 me?","answer":"38 waist and 46 length","votes":"0","username":"Arvind Jain","date":"2021-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"You can sent to switzerland?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Arvind Jain","date":"2021-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"My waistline is 32 inch .and the height 5.4 inch .this kurta dhoti fit or not .or what can i choose","answer":"Fit","votes":"0","username":"Arvind Jain","date":"2021-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cloth material","answer":"Cotton blend","votes":"0","username":"Darsh Creations","date":"2021-04-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want a Pyjama instead of dhoti..?? Is that possible..??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Arvind Jain","date":"2021-04-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564f0330bf91bd3102b0b"},"product_asin":"B07CQN3232","QAs":[{"question":"Deleviry time home","answer":"Awesome quality I have been using from last 3 years now also am wearing in function..","votes":"0","username":"Rohan…","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"I wear 36 size shirt which size is fitted on me","answer":"Take 38","votes":"0","username":"Rohan…","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the cloth good","answer":"Ouality of my product is very good","votes":"0","username":"Vaishali Ganorkar","date":"2020-03-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is pant is also there whith this???","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vaishali Ganorkar","date":"2020-03-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"I wear 39size shirt.. which size fits me??","answer":"38 size","votes":"0","username":"Neelkamal Meena","date":"2019-10-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"I wear 39size shirt.. which size fits me??","answer":"38 size","votes":"0","username":"Neelkamal Meena","date":"2019-10-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want XL, so which size is suitable, 42 or 44","answer":"44","votes":"0","username":"Swatideep","date":"2019-10-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"40 means M size?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anuradha","date":"2019-06-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564f1330bf91bd3102b14"},"product_asin":"B07CPWCHMY","QAs":[{"question":"Where is the size chart of 46","answer":"Xxxl","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-10-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much my size my hight 5.4 inch","answer":"40","votes":"0","username":"Ankur Rana","date":"2019-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"My height is 5'11\"..and chest 45inches... Size 40 is OK for me?? And for Patiala salwar which size is perfect??","answer":"Xl","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-10-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest is 32,what size i should buy in kurta ?","answer":"34","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-11-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is 40 slim fit. What size should I buy in kurta ?","answer":"You may go for size 40. However, it would be somewhat slim fit for you.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it layered with inner cloth(astar)","answer":"The kurta doesn't have an astart.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-06-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564f2330bf91bd3102b1b"},"product_asin":"B07284216C","QAs":[{"question":"What is the length of the sleeves?","answer":"Depends on the size you will order","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-11-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it really made by silk & cotton ?","answer":"No it's like synthetic little rough","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest size 38 solder 18 to mera size kya hoga","answer":"Xl try karate Tora tight hai sizes","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"If size not fitted then how to return ??","answer":"Prime member","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this man comes free with kurta and pajama ?","answer":"No this men is not original only for a dammy purpose but if you order it they will send you kurta or pajama set of good quality","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is its size","answer":"Xxxl","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pant is elestic or not","answer":"Not elestic","votes":"0","username":"DEEPAK S.","date":"2021-12-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to check pant size","answer":"There is free size pzama , it's narrow and zero size legs","votes":"0","username":"DEEPAK S.","date":"2021-12-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is xl which sixe i want to buy ?","answer":"42 Inc will perfect for you if you are healthy or 40 also came in xl","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please send my order early","answer":"Let amazon customer service know about it","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564f2330bf91bd3102b26"},"product_asin":"B07CPZ9ZKQ","QAs":[{"question":"Where is the size chart of 46","answer":"Xxxl","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-10-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much my size my hight 5.4 inch","answer":"40","votes":"0","username":"Ankur Rana","date":"2019-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"My height is 5'11\"..and chest 45inches... Size 40 is OK for me?? And for Patiala salwar which size is perfect??","answer":"Xl","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-10-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest is 32,what size i should buy in kurta ?","answer":"34","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-11-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is 40 slim fit. What size should I buy in kurta ?","answer":"You may go for size 40. However, it would be somewhat slim fit for you.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it layered with inner cloth(astar)","answer":"The kurta doesn't have an astart.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-06-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564f3330bf91bd3102b2d"},"product_asin":"B07NGM6H61","QAs":[{"question":"How to know the men size....the mentioned number is for chest or age for men","answer":"Order according to your shirt size","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-12-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to select  size  dad & son","answer":"Your shirt size","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-12-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get my stuff early delivery","answer":"Prime members","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-12-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it puore silk","answer":"how can u expect Pure silk  at such cheap cost","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-10-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this available with modi jacket","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-10-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is chest size for 36 man in your product","answer":"36 only","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-10-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this product returnable?","answer":"I don't know hether is returnable","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-10-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Family dress set father mother and child like king queen and children  photo picture in heart shape","answer":"U don't pic uploading option her","votes":"0","username":"vijayakrishna","date":"2020-10-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get early delivery","answer":"Dear Customer,Greetings of the Day!We would like to inform you that most of our orders are fulfilled by Amazon wherein Amazon looks after the logistics.We would also like to inform you that the material is in stock & can be immediately dispatched.Hence, we would request you to place the order.Happy Shopping!JBN Creations | VASTRAMAYsee less","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2020-08-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Men kurta xl or baby 3 year which size are perfect in above list","answer":"Perfectly fit and nice but the child was a bit older.","votes":"0","username":"DEEPAK KUMAR BACHHAL","date":"2020-07-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564f3330bf91bd3102b39"},"product_asin":"B07CQLRRNW","QAs":[{"question":"Is it of pure cotton..?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-10-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest size is 40 which size suitable for me?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Hariprasad prajapati","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest size is 40 which size suitable for me?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Hariprasad prajapati","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is Large (L) and my paint size is 32 which is fit for me","answer":"Yes ok","votes":"0","username":"Hariprasad prajapati","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is 40. My height is 168 cms which size is suitable for t","answer":"You may go for size 42.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-11-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is 40 and my hight is 5.8 which is fit for me","answer":"Go for 42.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-11-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564f4330bf91bd3102b40"},"product_asin":"B07D8RQ86X","QAs":[{"question":"my height is 5.3 what size will suit me ? and what is the cloth material ?","answer":"I had bought 40 size , which fits perfect on me .","votes":"0","username":"Raj","date":"2022-11-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"My height is 5.11 and weight is 85 kg plz tell me the correct size dhoti kurta  for for me","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suits for 6 feet?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size  & jeans(trouser size) is xl & 36 respectively, which size will be comfortable to me?","answer":"Hi.... try xxl...it's fit for u","votes":"0","username":"m r moinuddin","date":"2019-08-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"this suits fr a 5.6 height","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Hariprasad prajapati","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564f7330bf91bd3102b49"},"product_asin":"B08LMNQY2W","QAs":[{"question":"Is it with pajama or not?","answer":"The price is inclusive of a Kurta only","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it also include payjama?","answer":"The price is inclusive of Kurta only","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564f8330bf91bd3102b4c"},"product_asin":"B08QFDWR5D","QAs":[{"question":"Its difficult to find the matching pants for it can u please sell pyjamas also with this","answer":"Please refer to the below link","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have both kurta and pyjama?","answer":"The price is inclusive of a Kurta only","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Only kurta or kurta & payjama","answer":"The price is inclusive of a Kurta only.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-11-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"My Body size is 40 which size would will fit me?","answer":"You may go for size L","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-08-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564f8330bf91bd3102b53"},"product_asin":"B08WK7VP7S","QAs":[{"question":"Is this full set?? With pant","answer":"The price is inclusive of a Kurta only.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564f9330bf91bd3102b55"},"product_asin":"B08WK6KNW9","QAs":[{"question":"What size should i buy for 40 inch chest? other manyavar kurtas show m=38 inches but this one shows m=40 inches","answer":"Please refer to the size chart updated as an image.. For 40 inch chest, you may go for the L size...","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"642564fa330bf91bd3102b57"},"product_asin":"B08LMJD6S1","QAs":[{"question":"XL is 42 or 44. Pl confirm","answer":"42","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-12-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256501330bf91bd3102b5d"},"product_asin":"B08FHD7C6D","QAs":[{"question":"Brown colour hai isme kya","answer":"The other color in this item is blue.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-03-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256501330bf91bd3102b5f"},"product_asin":"B09FK6L58C","QAs":[{"question":"Is pyjama come with it","answer":"The product price is inclusive of a Kurta Only.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256502330bf91bd3102b61"},"product_asin":"B08KGNHX6Y","QAs":[{"question":"Does this kurta has pockets??","answer":"This Kurta comes with 2 side pockets","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-03-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pyjama included or not in package?","answer":"Nope . It was not in package","votes":"0","username":"kiran","date":"2020-11-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256502330bf91bd3102b64"},"product_asin":"B08LVC31C6","QAs":[{"question":"Does it contains pyjama?","answer":"The price is inclusive of a Kurta only.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-12-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256505330bf91bd3102b68"},"product_asin":"B09TT93LK2","QAs":[{"question":"Bro it is really good or not ?     It is real manyaver or not ?","answer":"It is original Manyavar brand product...","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-03-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256507330bf91bd3102b6a"},"product_asin":"B07J5529RH","QAs":[{"question":"Is there a pocket in the kurta?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Md Mahmood","date":"2022-01-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i wear it with Formal pant","answer":"Yes you can...","votes":"0","username":"VINEETH PILLAI","date":"2021-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is pant included","answer":"No. Only kurta.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-11-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"In rs800 only kurta ir both kurta + pant??","answer":"Just the kurta","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-10-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256509330bf91bd3102b71"},"product_asin":"B098JM8V2N","QAs":[{"question":"Does the payjama comes with it ?","answer":"no it is separate","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"dhoti is also there or just kurta only","answer":"just kurta only","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425650c330bf91bd3102b76"},"product_asin":"B07D8WFSNZ","QAs":[{"question":"Is it pure cotton silk?","answer":"I didn’t think so , ...","votes":"0","username":"Venkatesh S Guttedar","date":"2019-10-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"is the product raw silk?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"VASTRAMAY","date":"2019-09-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it only for kurta not with pant right?","answer":"Yes indeed it is just kurta.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-06-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425650d330bf91bd3102b7c"},"product_asin":"B098JMVKLQ","QAs":[{"question":"Where is your size chart?","answer":"It was nice perfect fit","votes":"0","username":"Anubinda","date":"2023-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this only kurta or kurta pajama?","answer":"Only kurta","votes":"0","username":"Dr Sreehari Rao Ramineni","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425650e330bf91bd3102b7f"},"product_asin":"B09CQ5KPXT","QAs":[{"question":"Is it only kurta??","answer":"Yes, only kurta.","votes":"0","username":"A Ghosh","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425650e330bf91bd3102b81"},"product_asin":"B07WMG1R74","QAs":[{"question":"Do phant will given with kurta","answer":"No only kurta.","votes":"0","username":"Ratna dey","date":"2021-12-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which size is perfect for 16 years","answer":"S size","votes":"0","username":"Ratna dey","date":"2021-11-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425650f330bf91bd3102b84"},"product_asin":"B098JHZY9M","QAs":[{"question":"How much is the. Chest size in 3xl","answer":"I use 6XL","votes":"0","username":"Dr. S.","date":"2022-08-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is only Kurta or or set of Kurta and Payjama?","answer":"Kurta only...","votes":"0","username":"Surendra Kumar","date":"2022-03-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256510330bf91bd3102b87"},"product_asin":"B08DM4R1KG","QAs":[{"question":"Does it come with the pajama as well?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"roshan singh","date":"2022-09-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have a pyjama in the set or only kurta??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"roshan singh","date":"2022-09-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this comes with payjama also","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"roshan singh","date":"2022-09-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the Kurtha come with white pant as well","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"roshan singh","date":"2022-09-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it only kurta or with salwar?","answer":"Only kurta","votes":"0","username":"roshan singh","date":"2022-09-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256511330bf91bd3102b8e"},"product_asin":"B07GNNBY3Q","QAs":[{"question":"Refund not received","answer":"You may remind through Customer service","votes":"0","username":"Vijay Bathina","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is lenth of 46 size?","answer":"Its knee length","votes":"0","username":"seeya","date":"2020-01-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's only kurta?","answer":"Yes only kurta","votes":"0","username":"seeya","date":"2020-01-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256512330bf91bd3102b92"},"product_asin":"B071HNP93G","QAs":[{"question":"What is the length of the sleeves?","answer":"Depends on the size you will order","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-11-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it really made by silk & cotton ?","answer":"No it's like synthetic little rough","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest size 38 solder 18 to mera size kya hoga","answer":"Xl try karate Tora tight hai sizes","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"If size not fitted then how to return ??","answer":"Prime member","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this man comes free with kurta and pajama ?","answer":"No this men is not original only for a dammy purpose but if you order it they will send you kurta or pajama set of good quality","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is its size","answer":"Xxxl","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pant is elestic or not","answer":"Not elestic","votes":"0","username":"DEEPAK S.","date":"2021-12-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to check pant size","answer":"There is free size pzama , it's narrow and zero size legs","votes":"0","username":"DEEPAK S.","date":"2021-12-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is xl which sixe i want to buy ?","answer":"42 Inc will perfect for you if you are healthy or 40 also came in xl","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please send my order early","answer":"Let amazon customer service know about it","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256514330bf91bd3102b9e"},"product_asin":"B07H33ZRV5","QAs":[{"question":"Is it both kurta & payjama or only kurta? Is that full set?","answer":"You have sent me only kurta for pajama I have made a complaint also even talked to your customer care,till today I am waiting for pajama.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2018-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Tell me percentage of fabric,means how much cotton and hiw much what,","answer":"40% cotton and 60% polyester.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its fully cotton or mixed","answer":"Mixed","votes":"0","username":"K.P. AHMED","date":"2018-04-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256515330bf91bd3102ba4"},"product_asin":"B098JKP569","QAs":[{"question":"Where is your size chart?","answer":"It was nice perfect fit","votes":"0","username":"Anubinda","date":"2023-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this only kurta or kurta pajama?","answer":"Only kurta","votes":"0","username":"Dr Sreehari Rao Ramineni","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256516330bf91bd3102ba7"},"product_asin":"B07H32ZLJY","QAs":[{"question":"What is the length of the sleeves?","answer":"Depends on the size you will order","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-11-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it really made by silk & cotton ?","answer":"No it's like synthetic little rough","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"My chest size 38 solder 18 to mera size kya hoga","answer":"Xl try karate Tora tight hai sizes","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"If size not fitted then how to return ??","answer":"Prime member","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this man comes free with kurta and pajama ?","answer":"No this men is not original only for a dammy purpose but if you order it they will send you kurta or pajama set of good quality","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is its size","answer":"Xxxl","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pant is elestic or not","answer":"Not elestic","votes":"0","username":"DEEPAK S.","date":"2021-12-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to check pant size","answer":"There is free size pzama , it's narrow and zero size legs","votes":"0","username":"DEEPAK S.","date":"2021-12-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"My shirt size is xl which sixe i want to buy ?","answer":"42 Inc will perfect for you if you are healthy or 40 also came in xl","votes":"0","username":"Preeti","date":"2022-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please send my order early","answer":"Let amazon customer service know about it","votes":"0","username":"BINITA SARKAR…","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256516330bf91bd3102bb2"},"product_asin":"B098JHF26L","QAs":[{"question":"How much is the. Chest size in 3xl","answer":"I use 6XL","votes":"0","username":"Dr. S.","date":"2022-08-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is only Kurta or or set of Kurta and Payjama?","answer":"Kurta only...","votes":"0","username":"Surendra Kumar","date":"2022-03-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256516330bf91bd3102bb7"},"product_asin":"B07TL4P6Q3","QAs":[{"question":"What is size 96","answer":"S","votes":"0","username":"mallesh","date":"2022-10-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"What size if for 44?","answer":"104 is XL/44","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the size of m","answer":"M would be size 40","votes":"0","username":"Hemant","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 100% cotton ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Hemant","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What size is L ?","answer":"42","votes":"0","username":"Hemant","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What size to buy for M?","answer":"40","votes":"0","username":"Hemant","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What size is S","answer":"S","votes":"0","username":"mallesh","date":"2022-10-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"What size is 3xl","answer":"104 is equal to XL","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-02-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256525330bf91bd3102bc7"},"product_asin":"B0B2KCN6GV","QAs":[{"question":"Only jacket or complete jacket with kurta available?","answer":"Only jacket","votes":"0","username":"Shashank","date":"2022-12-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256528330bf91bd3102bca"},"product_asin":"B08WHX5QGG","QAs":[{"question":"In size  L we got pijaam n jacket both but in size M we got nly jacket.. actually  we need full set..","answer":"The price is inclusive of a Jacket only.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2021-11-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256529330bf91bd3102bce"},"product_asin":"B0192VE6Z2","QAs":[{"question":"I have size 38 kurta payjama. Which size of jacket should I order.. 38 or 40?","answer":"38 (Medium)","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Material of cloth?","answer":"Nice Quality","votes":"0","username":"Sachin","date":"2019-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which fine quality fabric is used? Silk or cotton or some other?","answer":"It's a blended fabric which means a mix of cotton and silk.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-03-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"For how much time periodreturn/refund aplicable and conditions?","answer":"Same day","votes":"0","username":"Sachin","date":"2019-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"For how much time periodreturn/refund aplicable and conditions?","answer":"Please check the below link, hope this will help you","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2019-02-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Have you set with kurta pajama and jacket ??  And what is range of if i purchase all set ?","answer":"Yes we do have wide range of kurta set, starting from 6,999.","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2018-12-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"What wiill be my size with chest 40inch","answer":"Dear Sir","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2018-10-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is your 40size for kurta pajama","answer":"40 = Large Size","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2018-09-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you please provide this jacket for size 38 ?","answer":"Dear Roopa,Please note that 38 Size or Medium size is available with us. You can order itThanks & RegardsManyavar Teamsee less","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2017-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will i get d kurta n pyjama also with this jacket..???","answer":"Only jacket","votes":"0","username":"Bhanu","date":"2017-05-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256529330bf91bd3102bd9"},"product_asin":"B07DVD87VJ","QAs":[{"question":"Only nehru jackt ya with in kurta","answer":"The price is inclusive of Jacket only","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-01-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425652f330bf91bd3102bde"},"product_asin":"B09DPS8ZFJ","QAs":[{"question":"This jacket shoulder what size","answer":"Request you to refer to the image of the size chart for more detail","votes":"0","username":"VEDANT FASHIONS LIMITED","date":"2022-02-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256534330bf91bd3102be3"},"product_asin":"B09CSZ1MCT","QAs":[{"question":"What is the size of 44? its l or xl","answer":"XL","votes":"0","username":"Parvesh","date":"2023-03-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What size jacket is 3xl? 46 or 48?","answer":"I had ordered size 44 which fits me well","votes":"0","username":"Anil","date":"2023-01-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"XL is what 42 size of the koti?","answer":"42","votes":"0","username":"Sisir Das","date":"2022-09-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can a person wear in summer? Is it woollen mixed?","answer":"Why not?","votes":"1","username":"V19","date":"2022-02-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it suitable for winters?","answer":"Its more for dressing up smartly in very mild winters with temp not below 20 degrees.","votes":"1","username":"Anil","date":"2021-11-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Size Chart?","answer":"no video available but what the chart size says its perfect fitting.","votes":"1","username":"Anil","date":"2021-11-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256534330bf91bd3102bec"},"product_asin":"B07D92D8K7","QAs":[{"question":"We want quickly my order","answer":"Dear customer, thanks for showing interest in JBN Creation's ensemble. All our items are Amazon fulfilled and all logistics are taken care by Amazon personally. Request you to please call customer support for delivery inquiries. Thanks, JBN family","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-08-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256535330bf91bd3102bee"},"product_asin":"B07D8WND3Y","QAs":[{"question":"The photo is showing with kurta having calff with same material as that of the coat, pl calarify whether kurta is included or not","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Harjeet Singh Gora","date":"2021-01-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it kurta pajama set with  jacket","answer":"Its the jacket only no kurta. But trust me it is worth the price. Go buy it!","votes":"0","username":"Aditya Chatterjee","date":"2020-11-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is der return policy","answer":"The return policy if amazon is great. And obviously it is returnable...","votes":"0","username":"Aditya Chatterjee","date":"2020-11-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this included kurta and payjama","answer":"No it was jacket only.","votes":"0","username":"Adil","date":"2019-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Only jacket to full set","answer":"Only Jacket.","votes":"0","username":"Adil","date":"2019-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"This size is slim fit or regular fit ... please confirm","answer":"Regular fit.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-12-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is full kurta or only jacket","answer":"Only jacket","votes":"0","username":"Aditya Chatterjee","date":"2020-11-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 2 piece or 3 piece ?(including phyjama or not )","answer":"Just jacket","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-09-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"it is total set or only pijama with jacket?","answer":"It is just the jacket.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-08-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it full sleeve or sleeveless jacket??  Only modi coat or comes with kurta?","answer":"It is a sleeveless jacket.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-07-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256535330bf91bd3102bf9"},"product_asin":"B07XZMX897","QAs":[{"question":"Is it only jacket???","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, the product that you have chosen is only Jacket.Thanks & regardssee less","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2020-11-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do i know the size of man and kid? size as per chest waist ?","answer":"Dear Customer,You will find a drop down list of Sizes for both Father & Son.Also, beside the size you will find the size chart wherein all the sizes are mentioned.Thanks & Regards,see less","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2020-11-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256537330bf91bd3102bfc"},"product_asin":"B07RXLB1KG","QAs":[{"question":"New Brand","answer":"Fitting is not good quality is also not good and i didn't like it","votes":"0","username":"Irfan Ahmed Shaikh","date":"2022-01-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256537330bf91bd3102bfe"},"product_asin":"B07D8SXS44","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have pockets inside?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-12-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256539330bf91bd3102c01"},"product_asin":"B07XZN31VD","QAs":[{"question":"Is it with kurta set","answer":"I bought and got to return same as size was not at all matching to the order, also stuff was also not good","votes":"0","username":"Piyush Singh","date":"2022-01-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425653a330bf91bd3102c03"},"product_asin":"B07D8QVM65","QAs":[{"question":"Is it silk","answer":"Yes dhupion silk very good rich look","votes":"0","username":"Lucky","date":"2022-01-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Only jacket?no kurta and oajama?","answer":"Only jacket","votes":"0","username":"Lucky","date":"2022-01-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it fit for 46size","answer":"Select 46 size yes it will fit","votes":"0","username":"Lucky","date":"2021-08-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we get the pocket square as well ???? 😊😇","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Lucky","date":"2020-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Jacket is removable or not??","answer":"Yes removable","votes":"0","username":"sumanta biswas","date":"2019-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it cotton","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"rishabh","date":"2019-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it have return policy","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"rishabh","date":"2019-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it contains inner shirt and pant","answer":"No this is only jacket","votes":"0","username":"Gagan jindal","date":"2019-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"we also get kurta with jakcet?","answer":"No. This is only jacket when I bought.","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Sachdev","date":"2019-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Kurta and payjama included ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"rishabh","date":"2019-06-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425653a330bf91bd3102c0e"},"product_asin":"B07H34QX1X","QAs":[{"question":"Whc size is this..??????","answer":"40  inch","votes":"0","username":"ARUNA Enterprises","date":"2019-09-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you have the same shirt with 40 size","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for showing interest in our product. We suppose you would like to buy the shirt in size 40. We are glad to inform you that the required size is available in the portal and you can complete the buying of your desired product from there.RegardsSauravsee less","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2017-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you have the same shirt with size 42 or 44?","answer":"Dear Shane, thanks for your interest in your Vastramay's ensemble. Currently we do not have size 42 and 44 in stock, it is under production and we are hoping to add stock as early as possible. Please bear with us for few day. Thanks, JBN family","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2017-06-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425653b330bf91bd3102c13"},"product_asin":"B07XZMF5HG","QAs":[{"question":"Pajama included or not","answer":"Nope","votes":"0","username":"A A K","date":"2020-11-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Latest by when can you deliver this product for man-40 size & child 3-4 years size. is it possible to deliver by 10th nov if ordered by tomorrow 12pm.","answer":"No not in Covid Situation","votes":"0","username":"A A K","date":"2020-11-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this set completely given for us","answer":"Only Jacket","votes":"0","username":"A A K","date":"2020-11-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will they give Only baby dress","answer":"Baby Jacket","votes":"0","username":"A A K","date":"2020-11-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product contain full dress like including all three top, bottom , and jacket  ?","answer":"Only Jacket","votes":"0","username":"A A K","date":"2020-11-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Beta age in months???","answer":"Its Jacket only so not usefull","votes":"0","username":"A A K","date":"2020-11-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its a full set of kurta pajama or jacket ?","answer":"Just Jacket","votes":"0","username":"A A K","date":"2020-11-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its a with kurta pajama or only jacket ?","answer":"Only Jacket","votes":"0","username":"A A K","date":"2020-11-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425654a330bf91bd3102c26"},"product_asin":"B017M102Q6","QAs":[{"question":"Size details","answer":"Perfect","votes":"0","username":"manikanda kumaran k","date":"2022-01-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425654b330bf91bd3102c28"},"product_asin":"B07YFQ1LYB","QAs":[{"question":"My chest size 35 , let me know which label i can take","answer":"Dear Customer:We offer six sizes - Small = 36 (Chest - 40),Medium = 38 (Chest - 42),Large = 40 (Chest - 44),X- Large = 42 (Chest - 46),XX - Large = 44 (Chest - 48) andXXX - Large = 46 (Chest - 50).Please select as per your size.Thanks & regards,see less","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2020-10-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425654d330bf91bd3102c2b"},"product_asin":"B07NC38DS2","QAs":[{"question":"For man is it size or age ?","answer":"Size","votes":"0","username":"sachin","date":"2023-02-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Iwant to buy extra child dress","answer":"Good clothe material..good design","votes":"0","username":"sachin","date":"2022-10-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Baap beta kapda","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ankita","date":"2021-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to buy differrent color. Father age 29 Son age 4.6yr","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Priya katwal","date":"2019-10-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pakistani leather belts","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Rohit","date":"2019-10-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i buy only men set?","answer":"Under Baap Beta you can not.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2019-09-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i buy only men set?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Priya katwal","date":"2019-10-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it stiched?","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2019-08-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"May I know the colour of this dress?","answer":"The top is black with little shiney cloth.","votes":"0","username":"Jaswinder","date":"2019-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Man 30 and child 7 years available","answer":"You need to check as per size m,l so on","votes":"0","username":"Deepika","date":"2019-06-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6425654e330bf91bd3102c36"},"product_asin":"B07YFRTM82","QAs":[{"question":"Is it a pure silk","answer":"Yes, it is silk.","votes":"0","username":"AMIR KHAN","date":"2023-02-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Saiz kase btaye","answer":"Good clothes","votes":"0","username":"Rohit","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it include chunari?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sneh Jain","date":"2020-11-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256552330bf91bd3102c3d"},"product_asin":"B07J5JYWWJ","QAs":[{"question":"does it also have jutti in it","answer":"Nope..","votes":"0","username":"Imesh pal","date":"2021-10-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256556330bf91bd3102c41"},"product_asin":"B07CQM8FH9","QAs":[{"question":"Dhoti is incluuded or not","answer":"Dear Customer,This includes only the Kurta i.e. the top.If you want the dhoti also, please click on the below link.https://www.amazon.in/s?k=Vastramat+men+dhoti&i=apparel&ref=nb_sb_nossThanks & regardssee less","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2020-11-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pajama is include or not??","answer":"Included","votes":"0","username":"rahulagarwal","date":"2019-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it include this red dhoti?","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"Kanhaiya Gujarati Mochi","date":"2019-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is pajama also included?","answer":"This comes with a dhotuli","votes":"0","username":"Peeyush Kushwaha","date":"2020-11-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"If it doesn't fit can able to return it?","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"Kanhaiya Gujarati Mochi","date":"2019-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will pajama and shoe will be given?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-10-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256558330bf91bd3102c49"},"product_asin":"B07YFRGSY5","QAs":[{"question":"Is it gold paijama","answer":"Yes it was good.. I have ordered this to gift it my husband..","votes":"0","username":"Jyotsna Jaiswal","date":"2022-02-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"64256559330bf91bd3102c4c"},"product_asin":"B07CPVXJGV","QAs":[{"question":"How to wash this type of dress?","answer":"Preferably dry clean.","votes":"0","username":"Vastramay | JBN Creation","date":"2018-10-29 00:00:00"}]}
